What are you doing?
We don't stop here.
Get out of the car.
The boys found this on the floor,
in the back of the Caddy.
Yeah, they showed me.
Could be unrelated.
Could be.
Any of those dead kids
wearing pearl earrings?
No.
Could be someone's missing, maybe.
That’s what I'm thinking.
Just one more bag after that.
I just wanted to come here.
To Winkie's?
This Winkie's.
Okay. Why this Winkie's?
It’s kind of embarrassing.
Go ahead.
- I had a dream about this place.
- Oh, boy.
See what I mean?
Okay, so you had a dream
about this place.
Tell me.
Well...
it’s the second one I've had.
But they're both the same.
They start out that I'm in here but...
it’s not day or night...
it’s kind of half-night, you know?
But it looks just like this.
Except for the light.
And I'm scared like I can't
tell you.
Of all people...
you're standing right over there.
By that counter.
You're in both dreams
and you're scared.
I get even more frightened when
I see how afraid you are, and...
then I realize what it is.
There's a man...
in back of this place.
He's the one who's doing it.
I can see him through the wall.
I can see his face.
I hope that I never see that face
ever outside of the dream.
That’s it.
So... you came to see
if he's out there.
To get rid of this
god-awful feeling.
Right then.
It’s around the back.
Dan! Dan, are you all right?
What is it, Dan? Dan?
Hello?
The girl is still missing.
- Talk to me.
- The same.
I can't believe it.
Well, it's time to say
good-bye, Betty.
- It’s been so nice traveling with you.
- Thank you, Irene.
I was so excited and nervous. It was
sure great to have you to talk to.
- I'll watch for you on the big screen.
- Okay, Irene.
Won't that be the day?
Good luck, Betty dear.
- Take care of yourself and be careful.
- I will.
Thanks, again.
Betty, it was so nice meeting you.
All the luck in the world.
Thank you.
- My bags?
- Where to?
1612, Hayvenhurst.
Got it.
- Ten bucks says you're Betty.
- Yes, I am, Mrs. Lenoix.
- It is Mrs. Lenoix, isn't it?
- In all my living glory, baby.
- Pleased to meet you.
- Call me Coco. Everybody else does.
- Wait there and I'll go get the key.
- Okay, Coco.
Wilkins!
If that damn dog craps
in the courtyard one more time...
I'm just gonna bank his little butt for
breakfast! You don't have any pets?
- No, I don't.
- They're allowed.
I just don't like them
in here for obvious reasons.
There was a man that lived here once
that had a prizefighting kangaroo.
You just wouldn't believe what that
kangaroo did to this courtyard.
Let’s go see your aunt’s apartment.
It’s a good one.
I can hardly wait.
- It’s unbelievable!
- I told you.
You and your aunt probably have
an understanding, so here's the key.
And if you need anything,
just give a holler.
Everybody in this building is pretty
much okay with me...
or they wouldn't be here.
If you like, later on
I'll introduce you around.
Well, no hard feelings if you don't.
I'm sorry. My aunt Ruth didn't tell
me someone was gonna be here.
- I'm so sorry.
- It’s okay.
I'm Ruth's niece. My name is Betty.
I'm sure she told you I was coming.
There was an accident.
I came here.
I understand. I saw the dress.
I'm sorry. Are you all right?
What happened?
A car...
a car accident.
Are you okay?
I think so.
I was just...
taking a shower.
Oh, my God, I'm sorry.
I'll let you get back to that.
I'm gonna get unpacked.
What’s your name?
I'm sorry, I'll get out of here.
We can talk later.
My name is...
Rita.
Do you work with my aunt?
- No, I...
- I'm sorry...
it 's none of my business.
She has pretty red hair.
She's letting me stay here while
she's working on a movie...
that 's being made in Canada,
but I guess you already know that.
I couldn't afford a place like this
in a million years.
Unless, of course, I'm discovered
and become a movie star.
Of course, I'd rather be known as
a great actress than a movie star...
but sometimes people
end up being both. So...
that is, I guess you'd say,
the story of why I came here.
I'm sorry. I'm just
so excited to be here.
I just came here from Deep River,
Ontario, and now I'm in this...
dream place!
Well, you can imagine how I feel.
Sit down.
Where were you hurt?
- We should call a doctor.
- No.
- But this could be serious.
- No, I need to sleep.
If you have a concussion,
you shouldn't sleep.
I'll be okay if I sleep.
I just need to lie down
here and sleep.
You see, Adam, there
are some suggestions...
that ought to be brought forward.
And I know you said you would
entertain suggestions.
And that 's all anybody
here is asking you to do.
- What are you talking about?
- An open mind.
You're in the process of recasting
your lead actress, and I'm...
we are asking you to keep
an open mind.
What was it the last time?
- Okay, lets try the next one.
- He's not gonna like it.
We'll see.
Castigliani brothers!
Let me introduce you around.
Please...
take a seat. This is Mr. Darby,
whom you know.
And this is the director,
Adam Kesher.
And his manager,
Robert Smith.
She's very pretty.
May I offer you gentlemen anything?
- Espresso.
- Nothing.
- What 's the photo for?
- One espresso.
No, that 's it.
I think you're going to enjoy
your espresso this time.
I've done quite a bit of research...
knowing how hard
you are to please.
This one comes
highly recommended.
- What 's the photo for?
- It 's a recommendation.
A recommendation to you, Adam.
- It 's not a recommendation.
- This is the girl.
What girl? For what?
What is this, Ray?
We'd be happy to put her on the
list for considerations.
You'd be pleased to know, there's
quite a bit of interest in this role.
Interest? There's six of the top
actresses that want this thing.
This is the girl.
- Ray, take care of this.
- Hold on, hold on, Adam.
Hold on?
There's no way!
Napkin.
Pardon?
Of course.
Excuse me.
Is that all, sir?
- Shit.
- Sorry. That was highly recommended.
That is considered one of the finest
espressos in the world!
What 's going on here? There is
no way that girl is in my movie!
- This is the girl.
- Hey, that girl is not in my film!
It 's no longer your film.
This is the girl.
Castigliani brothers get out
of that limo?
- The two guys in dark suits?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
- Leave that door open.
Castigliani brothers?
Beat it, pal.
Good afternoon, Mr. Roque.
Her name is Camilla Rhodes.
The director doesn't want her.
Do you want him replaced?
I know they said...
Then?
Then...
that means we should...?
Yes?
Shut everything down?
Is that something that...
Do you want us to shut
everything down?
Then we'll shut everything down.
Oh, man, that 's unheard of.
An accident like that, who could
have foreseen that, man?
- It 's unreal, right?
- Yeah.
Unbelievable, man.
So, bro? God, you look good.
- What have you been doing?
- You know, just...
doing some stuff
for this guy.
Are you making ends meet?
Hardly.
I know, man, look at my digs.
Times are tough, bro.
Hey... man, it 's not that bad.
I hope you're not gonna
get in any trouble.
That was just a thing, man.
That story? That made you laugh!
- That was a funny story, man.
- Fucking car accident!
Hey, so that 's... that 's it, huh?
That 's Ed's famous black book.
The history of the world...
in phone numbers.
Oh, man!
Something bit me bad!
Hey, man!
She's hurt real bad! Could you come
here and call on the phone, please?
She's hurt real bad! You gotta
come in here and call the hospital!
Come on, man! I'm serious about this!
I can't do everything by myself!
Hey, man.
Oh, man!
Aunt Ruth, I'll try. I'm gonna study
those lines until I know them...
inside out.
Either right here on
this fabulous leather couch...
or I'll take them with
a coffee into the courtyard...
like a regular movie star.
I got a real shock to find your
friend Rita here.
She was in the shower
and I opened the door!
Rita!
What do you mean?
She was in an accident.
Rita. Your friend.
No, Coco unlocked the door.
No, she didn't see her.
She's sleeping.
I'm sure there's some explanation for
this. I don't think we have to do that.
Please, don't worry. Aunt Ruth,
we don't need the police.
You're awake.
I think I misunderstood.
I thought you knew my aunt
and that 's why you were here.
I just talked to my aunt on the phone
and she wants me to call the police.
Rita?
I'm sorry, I...
What is it, Rita?
I thought when I woke up...
I thought sleep would do it.
What 's wrong?
I just don't know who I am.
- What do you mean? You're Rita.
- No, I'm not.
I don't know what my name is.
I don't know who I am.
This is your purse.
Your name must be in your purse.
You wanna know, don't you?
- Yes, but...
- Open it.
- Sure you don't want anything?
- Not here.
- Thanks.
- A drink or something?
No. Thanks, though.
I'll take a cigarette,
if you have one.
Yeah, just reach inside my
shirt pocket there.
Any new girls on the street lately?
No.
I haven't seen any.
A brunette?
Maybe a little beat-up?
No.
- Keep your eyes open for me, okay?
- Sure.
You bet you will.
That money...
you don't know where it came from?
When you think of them,
the money and the key...
does it make you
remember anything?
There's something...
something...
there.
What did you say?
- They fired everyone.
- Who fired everyone?
Ray did!
Wait! I'm talking on the phone.
They closed the set. Everybody's
gone. You'd better get down here.
No.
You've gotta talk to Ray.
You've gotta fix this.
I'm going home.
Home?
Meet me at the office, we gotta do
something. You gotta do something!
- I'm going home, Cynthia.
- Adam, this isn't like you.
Please, come to the office. There's
gotta be something we can do!
I'm going home.
I wonder where you were going.
Mulholland Drive.
Mulholland Drive?
That 's where I was going.
Mulholland Drive.
Maybe that 's where
the accident was.
There must be a police report.
We could call.
We could call anonymously just
to see if there was an accident.
It'll be just like in the movies!
We'll pretend to be someone else.
I wanna walk around, anyway.
I'm in Hollywood and
I haven't even seen any of it.
Come on, Rita,
do you feel up to it?
Okay.
But just...
just to see.
Just to see if there was
an accident...
on Mulholland Drive.
Lorraine?
You're home?
Now you've done it!
Just forget you ever saw it.
It 's better that way.
What the hell are you
even doing here?
What are you doing?
That 's my jewelry!
- That bastard. You bastard!
- He's probably upset, Lorraine.
What are you doing?
Stop it!
Adam, stop it!
You're hurting me! Gene!
You're hurting me!
That ain't no way to treat your
wife. I don't care what she's done.
Throw him out!
Damn you, Adam!
Get out!
Let 's hide it.
There's one.
- Los Angeles Police Department.
- I'm inquiring about an accident...
...last night on Mulholland Drive.
- I'll connect you to Traffic.
- Sergeant Baker.
- Hi, I'm inquiring...
I heard a sound last night that
sounded sort of like a car crash.
I want to know if there was an
accident on Mulholland Drive.
Yes, there was.
- Can you tell me what happened?
- No, I can't.
- Was anyone hurt?
- May I have your name, please?
There was an accident.
He wouldn't tell me anything else,
but that was your accident, Rita.
Maybe there's something
about it in the papers.
Come on, I'll buy you a cup of
coffee and we can see.
Maybe it happened so late it 's
not in today's paper.
There's nothing?
Not that I can see.
That 's okay.
Thanks.
Diane.
Will that be all?
Would you like your check?
Rita, you want something?
- No, just... just the coffee.
- We'll take our check.
What is it, Rita?
I remember something.
I remember something!
- What is it?
- Diane Selwyn.
Maybe that 's my name!
"D. Selwyn." It 's the only one.
I'm gonna call.
- It is strange to be calling yourself.
- Maybe it 's not me.
Hello, it's me.
Leave a message.
That 's not my voice.
But I know her!
Maybe that isn't Diane Selwyn's
voice. Maybe that 's your roommate.
Or if it is Diane Selwyn,
she could tell you who you are.
Maybe.
Maybe, maybe...
Adam Kesher?
- Adam Kesher?
- Get lost!
- This is Adam Kesher's house.
- Like hell it is! Get out now!
Get out!
Adam Kesher?
Get out of here!
He's never coming back! Ever!
- Bastard.
- I guess you don't understand English.
She said leave. Here's the door.
Gene!
Get out!
Adam Kesher?
- Yeah, what is it, Cookie?
- I'm sorry, Mr. Kesher...
but there seems to be some
problem with your credit cards.
What? I pay you cash, Cookie.
Listen, two guys from
your bank came by.
My bank?
- How'd they know I was here?
- I don't know.
What 'd they say?
They said to tell you that you're
maxed out at your bank...
and that your line of credit
has been canceled.
That 's unbelievable.
Well, look...
I don't know what 's going on.
That is so much baloney.
- I got enough cash for you, Cookie.
- I know, I know. Don't worry.
But I'm sorry, it 's my duty
to inform you...
listen, man,
whoever you're hiding from...
they know where you are.
Right.
I'm sorry.
Hello?
- Someone maybe shut off my money.
- I know. Where are you, Adam?
- Sorry, what do you mean you know?
- Somebody called...
they told me you were as good as
broke. So I made a few calls.
- And?
- You're broke.
I'm not broke!
I know, but you're broke.
Where are you?
- I'm at Cookie's, downtown.
- Do you know somebody called...
"The Cowboy"?
- "The cowboy"?
- Yeah.
"The Cowboy". This guy,
the Cowboy, wants to see you.
Jason said he thought
it would be a good idea.
Jason thought it would be a good
idea for me to go see the Cowboy.
Should I wear my 1O-gallon hat
and my six-shooters?
Something tells me that this guy
is connected to what 's happening.
Adam, I think you should do it, and
you should do it right away.
- What 's going on, Cynthia?
- It's been a very strange day.
And getting stranger.
Where do I meet this Cowboy? Do you
have to ride out to the range?
Sort of, funny boy.
If I tell him the meeting's on...
you'll go to the top of the Beachwood
Canyon, there's a corral up there...
...where he'll be.
- You've gotta be kidding me.
Will you meet with him?
Yeah.
Sure. This has been
that kind of a day. When?
I'll call him right away
and then I'll call you back.
You know, you could stay at
my place, if you wanted.
- I don't think that 'd be a good idea.
- I was just offering a place to stay.
Yes, and I appreciate the offer,
Cynthia. I'll find a place.
Just go on and give that cowboy
a yodel and get on back to me.
Okay. But you don't know
what you're missing.
Just get along, little doggie.
And call me back.
It 's right about here. Sierra Bonita.
It 's not too far away.
What 's wrong with that?
I'm not sure about this.
I know you're afraid of something.
We'll be careful. I promise.
Tomorrow. We'll go over there...
and we'll find out.
It'll be okay.
It 's probably Coco.
- Yes, may I help you?
- Someone is in trouble!
Who are you?
What are you doing
in Ruth's apartment?
She's letting me stay here.
I'm her niece. My name's Betty.
No, it 's not!
That 's not what she said.
Someone is in trouble!
Something bad is happening!
I'm sorry, but I don't know
who you are and...
Louise?
What are you doing, Louise?
I've been trying to get hold of you
since 3 o'clock this afternoon.
That one is in my room and
she won't leave!
I want you to get her out.
I want you to get her out now.
This is Louise Bonner.
I'm sure she meant well.
Louise, this is Betty,
this is Ruth's niece.
I was on my way over here to see
Betty. Betty is a young actress.
I was delivering some faxed pages of
a scene for a big audition tomorrow.
- Well, here they are, honey.
- Thank you.
Come along now, Louise.
I'll take you home.
I'm sorry.
It happens sometimes. Come on.
No, she said it was someone
else who was in trouble.
Stop it, Louise!
I'm taking you home. Come on.
- Good night, Betty.
- Good night.
Good night.
Cowboy...
- Howdy.
- Howdy to you.
Beautiful evening.
Thank you for coming all the way
up here to see me from that...
nice hotel downtown.
No problem.
What 's on your mind?
Well, now. Here's a man who
wants to get right down to it.
Kind of anxious
to get to it, are you?
Whatever.
A man's attitude...
a man's attitude goes some ways
the way his life will be.
Is that something
you might agree with?
Sure!
Did you answer because that 's what
you thought I wanted to hear...
or did you think about what I said...
and answered 'cause you
truly believe that to be right?
I agree with what you said. Truly.
What 'd I say?
That a man's attitude determines to
a large extent how his life will be.
So since you agree...
you must be a person who does not
care about the good life.
How's that?
Well, stop for a little second...
and think about it.
Can you do that for me?
Okay. I'm thinking.
No, you're not. You're too busy
being a smart aleck to be thinking.
Now, I want you to think
and stop being a smart aleck.
Can you try that for me?
Look, where's this going?
What do you want me to do?
There's sometimes a buggy.
How many drivers does a buggy have?
One.
So let 's just say
I'm driving this buggy.
And if you fix your attitude,
you can ride along with me.
I want you to go back
to work tomorrow.
You were recasting the lead actress.
Audition many girls for the part.
When you see the girl that was shown
to you earlier today, you will say:
"This is the girl."
The rest of the cast can stay.
That 's up to you.
But that lead girl
is not up to you.
Now, you will see me one more
time if you do good.
You'll see me two more times
if you do bad.
Good night.
- You're still here?
- I thought that 's what you wanted.
- Nobody wants you here!
- Really?
My parents are right upstairs.
They think you've left!
- So? Surprise.
- I can call them. I can call my dad.
- But you won't.
- Lf you're trying to blackmail me...
it 's not going to work! You're
playing a dangerous game here.
You know what I want.
It 's not that difficult.
Get out!
Get out before I call my dad!
He trusts you!
You're his best friend.
This will be the
end of everything.
What about you?
What will your dad think about you?
Stop! Just stop it! That 's what
you said from the beginning.
If I tell what happened, they'll
arrest you and put you in jail.