- Before what?
- Before...
...I kill you.
- Then they'd put you in jail.
Then I cry, cry, cry,
and then I say with big emotion...
"I hate you! I hate us both!"
- Such a lame scene.
- But you are really good.
Thank you, darling.
Hi, there. Who are you?
Betty?
Betty, can I see you outside
for a minute?
What is it, Coco?
Your aunt called.
I was afraid of that.
She wants to know who's
staying in her apartment.
It 's just for a night or two.
Until she finds her own place.
I tried to explain that to aunt Ruth
but the connection was bad...
and her plane was leaving,
and she got it all mixed up.
I kept telling her
that it was my friend Rita...
and she kept saying
she didn't know any Ritas.
- Look at me straight, sweetie.
- Coco, she's very nice.
Honey, you're a good kid...
but what you're telling me is
a load of horse puckey.
Even though it
comes from a good place.
I'm gonna trust you
to sort this thing out.
- Thank you.
- Don't make me out to be a sucker.
Louise Bonner said there is trouble
in there, remember last night?
Well, sometimes she's wrong...
but if there is trouble,
get rid of it.
Is everything all right?
- Is it bad for you that I'm here?
- No, no, everything is A-Okay.
Now, I've gotta fix that sandwich.
And my audition is in one hour!
I hope I'm back
in a couple of hours.
- And don't drink all the Coke.
- Good luck.
When I get back, I'll keep the
cab waiting, so be ready to go.
"Voilà!"
Betty Elms, I would
like you to meet...
Jack Tutman, my assistant.
Woody Katz, who we have
cast in the part of Chuck...
and will do the scene with you.
Bob Rooker, our director...
and Julie Chadwick.
Now, our surprise guest,
Lynne James.
Alas, we can't afford her to
cast our show but...
well, as casting agents go,
she is the best.
Why, thank you, Wally.
Hello, Betty.
- Very pleased to meet you.
- This is my assistant, Nikki.
And the ever lovely Martha. Martha
Johnson, whom you met out front.
Hi.
So, shall we give it a go?
Would you like a water,
a coffee before we begin?
No, I'm fine.
Well then,
let 's everyone take a seat.
Betty, why don't you join Woody
over there and we'll play the scene.
Bob, do you have anything
you wish to say?
Something to Betty
before we begin?
No. It 's not a contest.
The two of them...
with themselves.
So don't play it for real...
until it gets real.
Okay.
Just tell me where it hurts, baby.
What?
I wanna play this one nice and close
like we did with that other girl...
what 's her name? With the black
hair. It felt good, what do you think?
That 's good, Woody. Just don't rush
that line again. I told you...
the line where you say:
"Before what?"
Bobby, acting is reacting.
I just play off them. They all say:
"They're gonna arrest you", like
that, and: "They'll put you in jail."
They say it the same way.
So when they say it, I just react.
- What 's your name?
- Betty.
Betty, look. You don't rush it,
I don't rush it, okay?
Now, we're gonna play this nice and
close just like in the movies, okay?
Dad's best friend goes to work.
Bob?
And...
action!
You're still here.
I came back.
- I thought that 's what you wanted.
- Nobody wants you here.
Really?
My parents are right upstairs.
They think you've left.
So, surprise!
- I can call them, I can call my dad.
- But you won't.
You're playing a dangerous
game here.
If you're trying to blackmail me...
it 's not gonna work.
You know what I want.
It 's not that difficult.
Get out.
Get out before I call my dad.
He trusts you. You're his...
best friend.
This will be the end
of everything.
What about you? What'll
your dad think about you?
Stop.
Stop it.
That 's what you said from
the beginning.
If I tell them what happened, they
will arrest you and put you in jail.
So get out of here...
before...
Before what?
Before...
I kill you.
Well, then they'd put you in jail.
I hate you.
I hate us both.
- I'm gonna take her over there.
- Yeah, big time.
Well, there it was.
Yeah, there it was, all right. Baby,
you got a way with you. Really.
Bob?
Very good. Really.
I mean, it was forced maybe,
but still humanistic.
Very good. Really!
Really.
Oh, I thank you, Betty.
And I really mean that, sincerely.
I mean, it was...
extraordinary.
You've done your aunt proud today.
I'm going to tell
her that first chance I get.
Now, you and I are going
to speak again very soon.
- Thank you, Mr. Brown.
- Thank you, Wally.
I'm sure you all have a lot to talk
about. We'll walk Betty out.
Yes, indeed.
And it was our pleasure, Lynne.
Don't you be a stranger around here.
We'd love to have you here.
- Come on, Betty.
- Thank you again, Mr. Brown.
And it was nice meeting
all of you.
Bye.
Bye!
She's a slam-dunk! Where
the hell did you find her?
God, that was awful!
Not you, Betty. You were stellar,
and I mean that. But poor Wally.
He'll never get that picture made.
Wally's days were up 2O years ago.
You know Woody Katz
is only doing it for a favor.
And the cast they have
so far is terrible.
Oh, God, terrible!
That poor old fool Wally.
He was very nice
and he seems so sweet.
And Wally... Mr. Brown is a very
close friend of my aunt 's.
Don't get me wrong, I love Wally.
I ought to, I was married
to him for 1O years.
And I love actors. All actors.
We just get a little catty sometimes.
We want to take you across and
introduce you to a director...
who's a head above the rest.
He's got a project
you will kill for.
Knock right out of the park!
Sixteen reasons
Why I love you
- One
- The way you hold my hand
- Two
- Your laughing eyes
- Three
- The way you understand
- Four
- Your secret sighs
They are part
of sixteen reasons
Why I love you
- Five
- The way you comb your hair
- Six
- Your freckled nose
- Seven
- The way you say you care
- Eight
- Your crazy clothes
That's just half
Of sixteen reasons
Why I love you
- Nine
- Snuggling in the car
- Ten
- Your wish upon a star
- Eleven
- Whispering on the phone
- Twelve
- Your kiss when we're alone
- Thirteen
- The way you thrill my heart
- Fourteen
- Your voice so neat
- Fifteen
- You say we'll never part
- Sixteen
- Our love's complete
Those are all
Of sixteen reasons
Why I love you
Sixteen reasons
- Cut it! Thank you very much, Carol.
- Checking the gate?
Checking the gate! Thank you.
We'll tell you what happens next!
Thank you very much for coming in.
I know how busy you are.
Are you kidding me? I loved the script.
Just show me where to sign.
I love you, but there's no way they're
gonna let me cast this thing...
until I've seen everyone. I'll let
you know as soon as I can.
I know you will. Because my manager
is gonna be bugging you. And me!
- My pleasure. Now get outta here.
- You're so cruel to me.
- I'm the girl who's playing this part.
- I'll see you later.
Hank? Where's Hank?
- Who's next, Hank?
- Camilla Rhodes.
- Is she ready?
- All ready.
- Bring her in.
- Camilla Rhodes, next.
"Sylvia North Story".
Camilla Rhodes, take one.
Okay, here we go.
Let 's lock it up, please.
- Roll sound, please.
- That 's fit.
Playback and action.
Why haven't I told you?
Oh, baby, I told
Every little star
Just how sweet I think you are
Why haven't I told you?
- Get Jason over here.
- Cindy, Adam wants to see Jason.
Made my heart an open book
Why haven't I told you?
Friends ask me
Am I in love
I always answer “yes"
Might as well confess
If the answer's yes
Maybe you may love me too
Oh, my darling, if you do
- Why haven't you told me?
- Did you want to tell something?
This is the girl.
Excellent choice, Adam.
Oh, my goodness.
I have to be somewhere.
I promised a friend.
- I'm sorry, I must go.
- Now?
Should be around here.
259O. That 's it.
Up there!
Does it look familiar?
- Don't stop!
- What is it? What do you see?
- Those men, in front, in the car.
- Do you know them?
Keep going.
Go around to the back.
Selwyn, number 12.
Now you got me scared.
You see?
I told you there was nothing
to be afraid of.
Betty, wait. Wait!
Don't.
No one's home.
Yes?
Diane?
Number 17.
But it said number 12.
I switched apartments with her.
She's in 17.
It 's down at the end, on the left.
But she hasn't been around
for a few days.
We'll leave her a note.
I'll go with you.
She still got some of my stuff.
You go ahead.
I gotta get that.
- Guess you're not Diane Selwyn.
- Guess I'm not.
There's still no one home, I guess.
- What are you doing?
- Come on, help me in.
Come on, I'll open the front door.
No!
Come on.
Come on!
I know what you're doing.
I know what you have to do.
But let me do it.
Let me do it.
You look like someone else.
Good night, Betty.
You don't have to wear
that in the house.
What?
The wig!
I was just looking at myself again.
I'll take it off to sleep.
You don't have
to sleep on that couch.
- No, it 's okay.
- No, it 's not. This is a huge bed.
Come on, just get in
and get a good night sleep.
It 's more comfortable than
the couch, isn't it?
Thank you, Betty.
It 's nothing. I shouldn't have let
you sleep on the couch last night.
No, I mean...
thank you for everything.
You're welcome.
Good night, sweet Betty.
Good night.
Have you ever done this before?
I don't know.
Have you?
I want to with you.
I'm in love with you.
Silence.
There's no band.
There's no orchestra.
Silence!
- Rita?
- There's no band.
Rita, wake up!
It 's okay. It 's okay.
No, it 's not okay.
What 's wrong?
Go with me somewhere.
It 's two o'clock. It 's two
o'clock in the morning.
Go with me somewhere.
Sure.
Now?
Right now.
There's no band!
There is no band!
This is all...
a tape recording.
There's no band, and yet...
we hear a band.
If we want to hear
a clarinet...
listen...
A muted trombone.
A muted trumpet.
It 's all recorded.
There's no band!
It is all...
a tape.
It is an illusion.
Listen!
Ladies and gentlemen,
let Club Silencio introduce to you...
"La Llorona de Los Angeles".
Rebekah del Rio.
I was all right
For a while
I could smile for a while
But I saw you last night
You held my hand so tight
As you stopped to say hello
You wished me well and you
Couldn't tell
That I've been crying
Over you
Crying
Since you said “so long"
I've been miserable and alone
Lonesome and crying
Crying
It's hard to understand
That upon seeing you again
I'd be crying
I thought
That I was over you
But it's true, so true
I love you even more
Much more than I did before
But darling, what can I do
You don't love me anymore
And I will always be
Crying over you
Your love has captured
The whole of my heart
That was left crying
Crying
Betty?
Where are you?
Hey, pretty girl.
Time to wake up.
- Where have you been?
- What do you want?
My lamp and dishes.
Come on, Diane,
it 's been three weeks.
I put your dishes in that box.
- That 's my ashtray.
- Take it.
- Anytime.
- I'm just making sure, Diane.
This is it?
By the way, those two detectives
came by again looking for you.
Camilla!
You've come back.
What was that you were saying,
beautiful?
I said...
you drive me wild.
We shouldn't do this anymore.
Don't say that.
Don't ever say that.
Don't, Diane!
Stop it!
Diane, stop!
I've tried to tell you this before.
It 's him, isn't it?
I'm not trying to show you how
to do the scene, but just...
watch me and I think you'll
understand what I'm getting at.
Don't sit so rigid, just...
just relax.
Now, the two of you are alone
and it 's real comfortable.
Like you've known
each other forever.
Even if you don't say anything,
it 's real comfortable.
Hank, can you just clear the set?
There's too many people around here.
- Let 's get this worked out.
- Clear the set!
Everyone have a cup of coffee.
- Everyone, please!
- Can Diane stay?
Yeah, sure, Diane can stay.
Hank, let Diane stay!
Diane!
Now, when she starts to cry,
don't pull her towards you.
Let her fall into you.
Just let her fall.
And when you kiss her...
it 's just a continuation
of that move.
There's no break.
Kill the lights!
Don't be mad.
Don't make it be like this.
Oh, sure, you want me to make
this easy for you.
No fucking way!
It 's not gonna be!
- It 's not easy for me!
- Diane!
Hello, it's me.
Leave a message.
Diane?
- Hello?
- Diane?
Camilla.
Diane, the car's waiting.
Are you okay?
You coming?
Good. It means so much to me.
Go on. The car's right
outside your house.
It's been waiting, okay?
Okay.
It's 698O, Mulholland Drive.
Mulholland Drive.
What are you doing?
We don't stop here.
A surprise.
Shortcut.
Come on, sweetheart.
It 's beautiful.
A secret path.
Perfect timing.
Welcome, Diane.
Well...
Here's to love.
Here she is!
I don't believe
you met my mother.
Hi. I'm Diane Selwyn.
Just call me Coco, everybody
does. Pleased to meet you.
Well, let 's eat!
I'm starving!
I'm sorry I was late.
I'm from Deep River, Ontario.
- A small town.
- So you rolled in here from Canada.
I always wanted to come here.
I won this jitterbug contest.
That sort of led to acting.
You know, wanting to act.
When my aunt died...
Anyway, she left me some money.
- She worked here.
- In the movies?
Yes.
How did you meet Camilla?
- On the "Sylvia North Story".
- Camilla was great in that.
I never went to
Casablanca with Luigi.
- What a pity!
- Then go!
I wanted the lead so bad.
Anyway, Camilla got the part.
The director...
Bob Rooker?
Yes.
He didn't think so much of me.
Anyway, that 's when
we became friends.
She helped me...
getting some parts in some
of her films.
I see.
So I got the pool,
and she got the pool man.
I couldn't believe it. I wanted
to buy that judge a Rolls Royce.
Sometimes, good things happen.
So I guess we've saved
the best for last.
- Do you want to tell them?
- No, you tell them.
Camilla and I...
are going to be...
Sorry about that.
No, I'm fine.
This is the girl.
Don't show me this
fucking thing here.
It 's just an actress' photo
resume. Everybody's got one.
You got the money?
I sure do.
Okay, now, once you hand that over
to me, it 's a done deal.
You sure you want this?
More than anything in this world.
When it 's finished, you'll find
this where I told you.
What 's it open?
Silence!
Silencio.